Nagase...
It's you, right?
And you're Taichi, right?
Yeah, people aren't going to
switch bodies every—
Wh-What's wrong?
Don't tell me that...
Did three people switch
bodies this time?
Maybe?
Yes!
I'm Kiriyama Yui!
I'm Aoki Yoshifumi!
I'm Inaba Himeko!
Want some more tea?
No thanks.
I can't take any more of this!
Why do I keep getting stuffed
in this yucky body?!
Why don't I get to switch
bodies with Iori?!
What? With me?
Uh, I think you're
missing something here.
I won't be stuck in this
body forever, will I?!
Hard to say.
Yesterday, they switched back
after thirty minutes.
Taichi, Iori-chan, shouldn't
you go to class?
I don't want to keep you
here because of us.
Nah, skipping class now and then is cool.
It's sort of exciting, almost
like we're a secret society.
Easy for you to...
Did you switch back?
Seems like it.
Yeah. Well, you know,
I don't think this is necessary,
but I have a reputation to keep,
so pretend like I'm grilling you.
Oh, I'm gonna keep on eating
since I'm having soba.
Can't let the noodles get soggy.
Well, you guys are
usually good students.
Though you've managed
to make me curious.
Man, I always choke on the first bite
when I eat something hot, you know?
Wait, that doesn't happen to you guys?
Just get it over with, Goto.
Now look here, Inaba.
I want to be considered an
open and friendly teacher,
so I let the students call me Mr. Go,
but that doesn't mean it's
okay to drop the mister.
You don't get to lecture me
until you start doing your job.
Who did the bookkeeping for our
class after the cultural festival?
Right, thank you very much.
Try not to mention that while
other teachers are around.
So why are we here again?
Oh, right.
What were you all doing?
The three of you, plus Aoki and Kiriyama
didn't show up until third period.
We all had some mini
chocolate buns yesterday
that turned out to be spoiled,
so we were all late due
to upset stomachs.
That's what happened.
Is that the same answer Aoki and
Kiriyama will give Ms. Hirata?
Of course.
If that's your story, I'll buy it.
You're excused.
Inaban's a real pro.
Yeah, she can lie through her teeth
and still come across all haughty like that.
She'll grow up to be a
scammer or con artist.
Seriously...
If you don't have anything
nice to say, shut up.
Did Aoki and Kiriyama get out of it okay?
Yeah. And?
What's wrong, Yui?
Hello?
What's wrong?
Did you see a ghost or something?
Oh, I need to go to the restroom.
Enjoy.
What to do?
I need to find a place
where I can be alone!
Whoa!
What are you doing in here?!
That's right.
Then I have no choice!
Hm?
Again?!
What is going on?!
Hello? Is this Taichi?
Yeah, that's right.
Is Kiriyama with you?
Yeah, Iori's trying to calm her down.
Where are you right now?
Me?
I'm in the
restroom.
Huh? Oh.
You switched back?
Y-Yeah...
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Hello?
Hello, Inaba? Can you hear me?
Why am I in the restroom?!
What was Taichi doing?!
Put Taichi on the phone!
Yaegashi...
It's our turn to clean
the restrooms today.
Don't run out on me.
Back to the restroom.
Huh?
You look tired.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
Sorry, it took a while
to finish up cleaning—
Taichi!
I have...
I have a question for you!
Wh-What is it?
What's wrong, Nagase?
What happened between you and
Fujishima-san while we were switched?!
Uh, nothing important...
I'll tell you if it
was important or not!
How often do we get to see
Iori-chan this flustered?
Uh, well...
I probably should have
said something sooner.
He played with my boobs!
How am I supposed to get married now?!
I had to do that to figure
out what was going on!
When you were in my body,
you went to the girls' restroom.
You couldn't have...
I was just trying to
find a place to hide!
Wait, that's not even important!
What matters is that...
Fu-Fu—
Fujishima-san is...
A-Are you okay, Nagase?
Why are you so upset?
And what's so special about Fujishima?
I've never seen Iori so stressed.
What's the 1-3 class rep like?
Perfect manners, stellar grades,
and the teachers love her.
She's a model student.
Forget that! Taichi!
How big were Iori-chan's boobs?!
Ow, hot!
We don't have time to waste on that!
If you really want to know,
I can just tell you.
Iori is a C cup.
While we're at it, I'm a B,
and Yui's an A.
Wh-What do you think you're saying?!
It's okay, Yui!
You might be lacking in
the boobie department,
but you've got it going on
in plenty of other areas!
Get that look off your
face! It pisses me off!
And I'm not lacking!
Smaller can be better sometimes!
Oh...
So Inaba is a B and Kiriyama is an A.
Don't just stand there and stare!
Let's focus on Fujishima-san!
What am I supposed to do?!
We should focus on the body swapping.
Hey, hello there.
Goto?
How long have you been standing there?
I just got here.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling under the weather?
I feel perfectly fine.
Since this man is much healthier
than he needs to be.
The problem would be that I
lack motivation, tenacity,
courage, spirit,
and all that other stuff, I guess?
Um... What's wrong, Mr. Go?
I came to see if you people were
panicking about the personality swap.
Mr. Go, how do you know about th—
Oh, could you stop calling
me Mr. Go or Goto?
That's not who I am.
Who...
...are you?
Who are you?
Yes, how do I respond?
I suppose that Heartseed
counts as my name.
Heartseed?
What does a little-known plant
have to do with anything?
Dunno?
Well, I basically play
the role of an observer.
I just happen to
be borrowing this Goto
person's body at the moment.
So you're something
else in Mr. Go's body?
That sounds about right, yes.
That means you have something to do
with our personalities swapping.
Yes... Well, then...
The five of you will randomly swap
personalities for the time being.
So who switches with who
and when they switch
is completely random?
Yes. Bravo, Nagase-san.
You're absolutely right.
And I'll be observing you.
But you don't have to worry
about me intruding on your privacy 24/7.
That would require effort.
Do you more or less understand
the current situation?
That was supposed to be an explanation?
Fine. Then I'll start asking questions.
First, why us?
And are you able to
control this phenomenon?
How do we make it stop?
What is your objective?
All excellent questions.
To answer your first question,
you seemed like a fascinating bunch,
I guess.
What's that supposed to mean?
Then, after you've
switched around a bit,
and I'm like, "Yeah, that was fun,"
it'll all stop.
That means you control when this stops.
Yeah...
Don't worry too much about this
and go on with your lives.
And don't bother trying to
figure out how it all works.
That's not the task
you've been assigned.
Also, I recommend that you
don't tell anyone else
about the personality swap.
That would make more trouble.
Good luck then.
I'll be cheering for you a little from
the smallest corner of my heart.
Wait!
Um...
I have more questions for you!
That's not the task
you've been assigned.
Don't expect us to shut up
and do whatever you say!
Hey! The hell?!
Let me handle this!
Sorry, Mr. Go!
No way!
Kiriyama!
See you around, then.
What's up with this whole
"shocking turn of events" deal?
Yui was a karate champion
in middle school.
Mr. Go wouldn't be able
to do that normally.
When I dropped by the faculty office...
Me?
I've been sitting here,
going through paperwork.
Huh?
How come I haven't made any progress?
Did I nod off?
It sounded like he
didn't notice a thing.
Dammit! This makes no sense!
No, if we think too hard about it,
we may be doing exactly what he wants.
Maybe we should ask someone for help?
I think that's a bad idea.
He said it would mean more trouble.
Yeah, we can't really
trust what he says,
but we don't want to
make this any bigger.
I don't want to make Mom worry.
Whenever our personalities switch,
we'll need to stay in contact and
establish the current situation.
Try not to let anyone see you.
If you're forced to interact with
other people, do the
best impression you can.
Got it?
Got it.
It's been a week since we
established the ground rules.
You people are too careless!
Who's made the most basic of mistakes
by going into the wrong restroom
while in the body of the opposite sex?!
Me.
Idiots! How can you screw that up?!
That's the first thing to watch for!
It's hard to break habits.
I just forget.
Don't forget!
You're making it harder for
us to go to the restroom!
Um, I have a proposal.
Can everyone use the restroom
regularly when they aren't switched?
I just told you it's harder for us
to go to the restroom now!
But if one of us girls gets the
urge to go while in Taichi
or Aoki's body, that means...
Ew! Yuck!
You don't have to be so mean about it.
Okay, Aoki and I will try our best.
Yeah, thanks.
Why are you so nice to Taichi?!
You shouldn't worry about it.
I've learned how to pee
while standing up.
What?!
You need to start worrying.
And were you serious about that?
Moving on.
What about our virtue? Our bodies?
Nothing to worry about.
Right, Aoki?
Yeah...
I'll admit that I get the urge to try
stuff when I'm in a girl's body,
but you don't need to worry.
I haven't had the opportunity
to go to the restroom.
Honestly?
I'm being honest here.
This is the kind of situation where
mutual trust is important.
I'm not going to do anything stupid.
That's true.
Hey, Iori, when I switched bodies
with you the other night,
there wasn't anyone else in your home.
Why was that?
It's not safe to leave
a girl alone at night.
Oh, right.
I never mentioned this,
but my parents are divorced
and I live with my mom.
And my mom is really busy.
Well, if you run into a thug,
just unleash the pepper spray
and beat the crap out of him,
and it'll be fine.
It's not fine!
Huh?
Thinking it's not a big deal is the
most dangerous thing you can do!
We can't wait until
something goes wrong!
Uh...
Sorry.
Y-Yeah...
I'm sorry, too.
How long is this going to last?
Who is that Heartseed guy?
Oh, so this is what Aoki sees.
He's so tall.
Are you Nagase?
Correct.
Oh, Yui looks so tiny.
I-It's not what you think.
I don't have a problem
with Iori touching me,
but I moved away because
you're Aoki right now.
Yeah, I understand.
That wasn't very sensitive of me.
It's taking longer to go
back to normal this time.
What's wrong, Nagase?
I screwed up.
Are you talking about what
happened with Kiriyama?
Or is there something else on your mind?
Anything I can help with?
Time for Nagase Iori to
ask Taichi questions!
What's this?
Each one of us implicitly has
a soul, mind, and personality
which contributes to our identity.
Now that Nagase Iori's soul
is inside Aoki's body,
the result is identified as Nagase Iori.
However, souls and personalities
cannot be seen or touched.
That's why we typically use
physical appearance to identify a person.
That means that our bodies
are the foundation for the identity.
But if our bodies lose their significance
because of the personality switching,
will we still be ourselves?
Nagase?
Just kidding.
Whoa!
Hey, Taichi!
Oh, welcome back.
Whew, I'm back.
I finally returned to my own body.
Nagase seemed different somehow.
Well, maybe I'm overthinking it.
Hm, so that's how it goes.
What's that supposed to mean?
Hm? What's going on?
Oh. Nah, it's nothing.
Listen up, everyone.
We need three people from our class to
volunteer for the off-campus clean up.
Any takers?
What? There wasn't any warning?
Mr. Go probably caved again.
I'm too busy with practice.
Yes, yes. I know.
I'll volunteer, so we
only need two more.
What?
I'll volunteer.
Huh?
Oh, Inaba-san.
You'll help?
I... I'll also volunteer.
Really?
Work hard, Taichi!
Cut it out.
Let me go.
My day's been ruined, and
it's all your fault.
I'll make up for this later, so
cut me some slack, Inaba-san.
Yaegashi-kun, do you have a moment?
I have something I want to ask you.
What is your relationship
with Nagase-san?
What?
Friends in the same club?
Or something more?
That's right.
Wait!
This is a good opportunity
to make this clear.
H-Hey, what are you going to tell her?!
Iori is mine!
Stay away from her!
I'm in love with Nagase?
Whenever there's a guy
around, I start to shake.
Y-Your eyes are kinda scaring me.
Just let me handle this.
Sure. If that's what you want, Mom.
Selfless freak.